mpora.com 2017-01-29

# Privacy Policy - Factory Media

This Privacy Policy (the ‘Policy’) forms part of the Terms and Conditions for the access and use of this Website (the ‘Terms’) and should be read in conjunction with the Terms. Your access and use of this Website and any information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Policy and to our Terms. This Policy may be updated from time to time and you should read it each time you use this Website to ensure that you are happy with it. If you do not accept the contents of this Policy and the Terms then please do not use this Website. By visiting this Website, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy, terms and cookie policy. 

This Policy provides information about the use and disclosure of personally identifiable information collected about you on the Website. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. 

* * *

  1. The minimum age for members is 13. Please do not try to become a member if you are younger than 13. If you are under 13 and have joined we will delete your information as soon as possible after learning this. Please advise us if you believe we have personal information relating to a person younger than 13. 

Minors 13 years or older must ask their parents’ permission before providing personal information to us on the internet. Personal information placed on the Website will, subject to any privacy preferences set by you, be available on the internet. 

* * *

  2. You acknowledge that any personal details and material (videos, images, or other content) posted by you on the Website is published material and ceases to be private; such material is not considered to be personally identifiable information and is therefore not subject to this Policy. 

This Policy only applies to this Website and our other Websites, but not to any external websites or other organisations, companies, individuals to which we provide links or any advertisers or merchants who use our Website. It does not apply to those external websites, applications, and entities which we do not control. 

This Policy is concerned with governing the type of information and the manner in which we collect and store personal information about you and your use of the Website, the way that we use such information and the circumstances in which we will disclose information about you. 

* * *

  3. In order to register an account with us, you need to provide us with certain personally identifiable information (including your name, surname, date of birth, sex, email address, mobile phone number, IP address, country, address and postcode, sports interests, your activity on the Website (for website improvement purposes) and a profile image). We also ask you whether we can contact you with offers from us (and others) and in what ways we can communicate with you. You warrant that the personal information which you are required to provide when you register with us is true, accurate, current and complete in all respects. If any of the information you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your email address or name, or if you wish to cancel your registration, please email your new details to [admin.mpora.com](mailto:admin@mpora.com). 

Once you are registered with us, you can participate in various activities on our Website, including, but not limited to posting messages in our forums or the video comments section, creating blogs, uploading pictures and/or videos, posting material on your profile, participating in surveys, entering competitions and taking advantage of promotions, subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 

When you register with us, you will have the option of opting in to receive various email subscription newsletters. We may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our Website or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please log into your Mpora profile and unselect the unwanted newsletter or follow instructions on the bottom of any newsletter(s) received to unsubscribe. 

* * *

  4. When you visit our Website, we may send you one or more cookies to make the Website easier to use. Cookies are small text files that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser and to provide features such as automated login on your next visit. Cookies also enable us to personalise our content to your tastes based upon information that you have provided to us, such as an interest in a particular sport. Cookies in themselves do not contain any personal data, and can only be read and understood by the webserver that issued them. 

You can set your browser so that it will not accept cookies, but some components of the Website may not function properly or efficiently if you cannot accept cookies. 

When you visit our Website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever it visits any sites. The information recorded will include your IP address, browser type, web request, URLs, domain names and other technical data. 

We may also employ the use of other technologies to track the online usage pattern of our Users in our Website but such tracking will not be personally identifiable. 

**  
Read more about our cookie policy  
**

* * *

  5. If you register with us and submit any personally identifiable information to us, we will use your personal information to operate, maintain and provide you with the services and interactive functionality of our Website. 

Any pictures/and or videos that you provide to us for uploading may be redistributed through the internet and other media and may be viewed by the public. 

You can limit the spread of your personal information on the Website by opting out of the provision of some of your personal details. If you voluntarily disclose on the Website any personal information then this becomes publicly available and may be collected by others. 

We may arrange with other websites and advertisers to share aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring usage of our Website to help us develop our Website and the services we offer. We may provide the aggregate information to third parties from time to time, but these statistics will not include personally identifiable information. 

We will not sell your personal information to third parties without your consent; we will not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or unless you have specifically opted in to a particular feature, for example, a newsletter. 

We may use your personal information for non-marketing, administrative purposes. 

You can control how you share your personal information on the Website by opting out of the provision of some personal details. Other details such as your full name, username, country, sex, sports interests and date of birth (if you opt in to this) will be publicly available. If you remove or limit personal details later these may continue to appear elsewhere. When you click on links you will go to other site(s) and we are not and cannot be responsible for those sites. 

* * *

  6. The internet is not a secure medium. We have, however, put in place various security procedures to help to protect your personal information. Protection technologies we use include industry recognised firewalls, browser certification, password protection and limited access to personal information. 

We keep your personal information confidential. Our internal procedures cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information. 

We do not represent, warrant or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and any transmission is carried out at your sole risk. Once we receive information we have our own security systems in place, but we do not represent or warrant or guarantee that such systems cannot be breached. Although we will take steps to protect your personal details and you have some options to limit these no security measures are perfect and we cannot promise that only authorised people will access your personal information 

If our security systems have been breached, then we will take appropriate steps to remedy this and to notify you of any breach. 

* * *

  7. If any of the details you have provided to us change, then it is your responsibility to inform us of any such changes.

* * *

  8. We may provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We may share information that is not personally identifiable (such as anonymous User usage data) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on our Website. 

We will disclose your personal data, personally identifiable information and your User activity and any other details if we are requested to do so by law or by any regulatory or governmental authority or by any law enforcement agency, or upon receipt of a court order or summons or a legitimate request by a third party (for example, the police) in investigating illegal activities to provide information concerning your activities on our Website. 

We reserve the right to disclose information that we believe is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to protect the security or integrity of our Website, and to protect our Users and our Users’ rights, property, or personal safety. 

We do not provide any personally identifiable information to any advertisers, merchants or other Users. If you engaged with any advertisers, merchants or other Users on the Website, for example, in the Marketplace, then the terms in this Policy are not applicable to such arrangements and you should find out what privacy policies such third parties have in place. 

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who works for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, amongst other things, the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. 

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Please do not share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features with a view to preventing unauthorised access.

* * *

  9. We reserve the right to assign any data that we have collected about you to any third party purchaser. We may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, used or managed in the unlikely event that we become insolvent, subject to administration or enter receivership. In the event of a sale, transfer, reorganisation or other disposal, in whole or in part, your details may form part of the transferred business assets and as such may be shared with our advisors and any prospective purchasers and their advisors. 

* * *

  10. By submitting your information, you consent to the use of that information as set out in the Policy. The Policy may be revised periodically and we will give you notice of the details of new policy. 

If we change our Policy we will post the changes on this page and may place notices on other pages of the Website. We will indicate at the top of this page the date the Policy was last amended. 

* * *

  11. The capture, storage and use of your data is governed by the Data Protection Act 1998. This Act also gives you the right to access information held about you. We are registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office as a Data Controller, with registration number Z1289659. Our registration can be confirmed by searching the Register of Data Controllers on the [www.ico.gov.uk](http://www.ico.gov.uk/) website. 

Should you wish to obtain a copy of any personal data we have about you, please email us at privacy@factorymedia.com. We will provide you, with a readable copy of your personal data within 40 days of your request. The cost in most circumstances will be £10 per application. If the cost of processing your application is more than £10 we will notify you before proceeding. 

Before we provide you with a copy of any personal data we retain about you, we may ask for proof of your identity. 

If you consider that the information that we have about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, you must inform us promptly, so that we can make the necessary amendments. 

If you have any queries regarding our Policy, please email your query to [privacy@factorymedia.com](mailto:privacy@factorymedia.com)

##### Newsletter Terms & Conditions

Please enter your email so we can keep you updated with news, features and the latest offers. If you are not interested you can unsubscribe at any time. We will never sell your data and you'll only get messages from us and our partners whose products and services we think you'll enjoy.

Read our full [Privacy Policy](https://factorymedia.com/privacy) as well as [Terms & Conditions](https://factorymedia.com/terms).

_Cookies help us deliver our services._ By using this website, you agree to our use of cookies. [ Learn More ](https://mpora.com/about/privacy)

__**Accept**

production
